Ted:我们说到哪了?
Ted:Okay where were we?
那是2006年的七月, 我们的生活刚发生了意想不到的变化
It was June of 2006,and life had just taken an unexpected turn
爸, 你就不能把开头省了 直接说你是怎么遇见妈妈的吗?
Dad,Dad, can't you just skip ahead to the part where you meet Mom?
我觉得你已经说了有一年了
I feel like you've been talking for like a year
宝贝, 我告诉你的这些都是很重要的
Honey, all this stuff I'm telling you is important.
这些都是故事的组成部分
It's all part of the story.
我能去下厕所吗?
Could I go to the bathroom??
不行
No.
2006年的夏天既美妙又糟糕
The summer of 2006 was both wonderful and awful.
对我来说 开始是很不错的
For me, it started out great
事实上, 第一天简直棒极了
In fact, day one was amazing.
我终于和Robin在一起了
I'd finally gotten together with Robin.
然而, 当我正在享受一生中最开心的一天时
But while I'd been off having one of the best nights of my life,
你们的marshall叔叔却度过了最悲伤的一天
your uncle marshall had been having one of the worst nights of his.
marshall: 那就这样了?
marshall: So that's it?
我们分手?
We're breaking up?
Marshall, 对不起
Marshall,I'm sorry.
我只是...
I just...
我只是要去旧金山做这个艺术项目 脱离这个小圈子想一想我到底是怎样的人
I just need to go to san francisco and do this art program and-and figure out who I am outside of us.
能达成这个目的的唯一方法就是...
And the only way that I can do that is if...
我们这段时间不要联系了
if we don't talk for a while.
这段时间
For a while.
倒不如永远别联系, 好吗?
Try never,okay?
如果你从这个门走出去 我们就完了
You walk out that door,and we're done.
你再也不会听见我的声音
You're never going to hear my voice again.
我应该打给她
I should call her.
- 不 - 是
No,no. Ted it is--
如果她叫你别打给她你还打 那只会示弱, 你会后悔的
if you call her when she asked you not to you're just going to look weak and you're going to regret it.
现在, 听着 如果你觉得想找她，就先来找我
Now,listen,whenever you feel like calling her,you come find me first.
我会给你脸上来一拳的
And I will punch you in the face.
你是个好朋友, ted
You're a good friend,ted.
你听说大新闻了吗?
So,did you hear the big news?
你是说lily和marshall分手这件事
You mean how lily and marshall broke up,
而且lily走了, 昨晚没有比这件更大的事了 我想他已经知道了
and lily's gone and nothing else even remotely important happened last night,yeah,I think he knows.
哦, 天
Oh,my god.
我很遗憾
I-I'm so sorry.
怎么回事?
Wh-- what happened?
恩, 她离开了
Well,she left.
而我都不知道她会不会回来
And I don't even know if she's coming back.
我醒了才听到留言
I didn't get your message until I woke up.
老兄, 我很遗憾 多谢
Bro,I am so sorry. Thanks.
我知道这很难受
I know it must be tough,
但是你准备好听一些不仅能让你振作起来 而且还能让你兴奋的东西了吗?
but are you ready to hear something that will not only make you feel better,but will actively excite you?
当然
Sure.
有史以来第一次, 我们三个人都是单身了
For the first time,ever,the three of us are single at the same time.
我梦想着有这么一天 这将成为一个传奇
I've dreamed about this day,boys,and it's going to be legendary.
我们一起, 将会得到这个城市
Together,we will own this city.
当女生们想要报复她们前任男友时 我们就会出现
Anytime a girl wants to get back at her ex-boyfriends,we'll be there.
当女生们想要理清他父亲的问题, 想痛饮时 我们就会出现
Anytime a girl wants to solve her father issues through promiscuity and binge drinking,we will be there.
当一个单身舞会举行的时候
Anytime a bachelorette party drives through the city in a limo,
当她们把头伸出天窗外叫 "纽约, 这是怎么了?"的时候
sticking their heads out the sunroof shouting,"What's up,new york?
我们就是纽约的精髓所在
" We will be what is up new york.
绅士们, 我们将要着手于...
Gentlemen,we are about to embark on...
哦, 伙计们, 你们俩搞上了 对吧?
aw,man,you guys did it,didn't you?
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
sync:fisherchen www.YDY.com
这个夏天我学到了一样东西 那就是爱情开始的时候
One thing I learned that summer is that when love is beginning...
以及结束的时候, 头30天是惊人的相似
and love is ending,the first 30 days are remarkably similar.
比如, 你花了大部分时间在床上
For one thing,you spend most of your time in bed.
你的朋友没法忍受听你说话
your friends can't stand to listen to you.
他真是难搞
He's so ticklish.
真是一首好歌
It was a really beautiful song.
所以...
So...
真笨
stupid,man.
而且你似乎总是不穿裤子
and you never seem to wear pants.
嘿,marshall.
hey,marshall.
嘿, Ted
Hey,ted.
饿了吗?
You hungry?
你想说什么? 我的确想吃点什么
What's the point?I could eat some food.
他们就快离开我了
It's just going to leave me.
好吧, 至少在这个情境下,是你把食物给拉出来的(双关语dump,甩,窝屎)
Well,at least in that scenario you get to do the dumping.
快点, 今天是周日 应该吃点煎饼
Come on,it's sunday.It's pancakes day.
Lily以前总是做煎饼吃
Lily always made the pancakes.
上帝啊, 我爱吃她的煎饼
God,I loved her pancakes.
软软的
So soft.
热乎乎的
So warm.
样子还很好看
So perfectly shaped.
我们是不是还在讨论她的煎饼?
Are we still talking about her pancakes?
拜托, 你必须得吃点东西 想要我给你带什么?
Come on,you got to eat something; what can I get you?
啤酒
Beer.
不行, 你昨晚晚餐就是喝这个
No,that's what you had for dinner.
行
Fine.
那我就喝剩下的
Then I'll just have leftovers.
Barney: 那么他呆在家里一直都不睡觉?
Barney: So,he stays home all the time not getting laid?
看到了吧, 和你有了未婚妻一个样
No,see,that's what you do when you have a fiance.
他应该也来这了庆祝一下
He should be down here celebrating.
他反正有空
He's free.
他刚把红头瘤给切了
He got that redheaded tumor removed.
你应该写儿童读物
You should write and illustrate children's books.
你们知道Marshall最该做什么吗?
You know what marshall needs to do.
他应该停止悲伤
He needs to stop being sad.
我伤心的时候不会表现出伤心 相反我会表现的很出众
When I get sad,I stop being sad and be awesome instead.
的确是这样的
True story.
这才1个月
It's only been a month.
他有自己处理事情的节奏
He just needs to go at his own pace.
话又说回来, Lily是这些麻烦的始作俑者
Anyway,lily's the one who caused this whole mess.
嘿, 放过她吧 她也是我们的朋友
Hey,cut her some slack.She's our friend,too.
她只是想证明她是谁
She's just trying to figure out who she is.
证明她是谁?
Figure out who she is?
是的, 那她应该打电话给我 我有一整张列表
Yeah,she should call me; I got a whole list.
她自私
She's selfish.
她不成熟
She's immature.
她...
She'S...
什么?
What?
上帝啊, 你的眼睛好蓝
God,your eyes are so blue.
哇哦, 泰迪熊
Aw,teddy bear.
哦那真是...
oh that's A...
是的，想伤心也伤心不起来
yeah,it was hard to feel too bad.
我和我梦寐以求的女孩交往了 一切都是这么完美
I was dating the woman of my dreams,and things were going great.
好吧, 大部分的时候是这样的
Well,for the most part.
我找到了她的洗发水
So,I found her shampoo.
我想是她忘记带走了
I guess she left it here.
闻上去有她的味道
It smells like her.
像熏衣草的, 贝壳的还有希望的味道
Like lavender and seashells and hope.
不知为何, 性欲和舒适同时存在
Somehow,erotic and comforting all at the same time.
那是我的洗发水
That's my shampoo.
哦抱歉
Oh,sorry.
嗯, 我想他永远都不会睡觉的
Mmm,I thought he'd never go to sleep.
已经完了?
Already?
他在打电话给她
He's calling her.
- 我什么都没听到 - 他在打电话给她
I don't hear any-- he's calling her.
不
No.
好吧, 你是对的, 我不能打电话给她
Okay,you're right,I won't call her.
我不会打电话给她的
I will not call her.
好吧, 我打了
Well,I called her.
而我得到的是, 她换号码了
And get this,she changed her number.
就像我会缠着她不放似的
What,like I'm going to stalk her,or something?
她以为她很特别
Like she's so special.
就像只有她一个人叫Lily Aldrin
Like she's the only lily aldrin out there.
因为光在旧金山就有4个人叫这个名字
'Cause there are four others in the san francisco area alone,
根据我和他们的简短对话来看 任何一个都要比她强
and they all seem a lot better than her based on the brief conversations I had with them.
他知道我在里面吗?
Does he know I'm in here?
是的, 嘿, Robin
Yeah,hey,robin.
话说回来, 其中一个Lily Aldrin说...
Anyways,one of the lily aldrins said...
这必须停下来
this has to stop.
Ted, 我们才刚开始交往
Ted,we just started dating.
我们同意进展不要太快 而现在我们有了孩子
We agreed we don't want to move too fast,and yet somehow,we have a baby.
他不能自己养活自己
He can't feed himself.
他没日没夜的哭 让我们也没法睡觉
He cries a lot,he keeps us up all night.
你考虑过母乳喂养了吗?
Have you tried breast-feeding?
就是这样的!
Nailed it!
听着, 他们在一起9年了
Look,they were together nine years.
现在才1个半月
It's only been a month and a half.
他只是需要用自己的节奏走出来
He just needs to go at his own pace.
他昨晚睡在我们房间的地板上了, Ted
He slept on our floor last night,ted.
他只是看了一部恐怖片而已
He watched a scary movie.
是该严厉的爱了
It is time for some tough love.
我们需要让他走出那个公寓
We need to get him out of that apartment.
呼吸一点新鲜空气
He needs fresh air.
他需要阳光
He needs sunshine.
嗯, 阳光
Mmm,sunshine.
现在让我们热烈欢迎, Sunshine
Please welcome to the stage,sunshine.
好吧, 我不认为这对我有什么好处
All right,I really don't think this is going to help.
你知道你为什么还没有忘记Lily吗?
Do you know why you're not over lily yet?
因为你还能记起她赤裸的样子
It's 'cause you can still picture her naked.
当你忘记她的乳房的时候, 你就忘记了那个女的 这是科学真理
You can't get over a woman until you can no longer picture her boobs; it's a scientific fact.
平均每个男人脑子里只能储存一定量的乳房影像
The average male brain can only store a finite number of boob images or "b-pegs".
图片的格式是Jpeg,此处Barney自由发挥B(oob)-peg
而你的脑子里现在全部都是Lily的
And your hard drive's filled to capacity with lily'S.
有很多
There are a lot of them.
除非你重新输入别的女人的图片 不然它们永远都在那里, 不会消失的
Well,they won't go away until you overwrite them with images of other women's boobs.
这次旅程也许会有成千上万的乳房让你看 我们今晚就从这里开始, 朋友
Now,this journey may take as many as a million boobs,so we begin here tonight,my friend.
2个一次
Two at a time.
这些可以算是4个
Those count as four.
很有趣, 是吗?
This is fun right?
我们在户外, 天气很好
We're outside,it's a beautiful day.
Indians要赢了
The indians are winning.
我不得不承认, 呆在户外的确好受多了
I got to admit,it is really nice to be outside.
朋友们, 请将你们的注意放到这个 非同寻常的戒指身上吧
Yankee fans,please turn your attention to the diamond vision for a special seventh-inning-stretch surprise.
哦不
Oh,no.
这是一个大谎言
it's all a big lie!
她会让你伤透心的
She's just going to break your heart.
你能把我从这里拖出去 但是她是一个没有灵魂的空壳
you can drag me out of here,but she has no soul!
我们什么都试过了, 棒球, 脱衣舞女
We've tried everything-- baseball,strippers.
那个家伙还是不买一点帐
The guy still won't eat a damn pancake.
我觉得他已经没希望了
I think he's beyond repair.
看, 这就是你们男人的通病
See,this is the problem with guys.
你们根本不知道怎么处理心碎的问题
You don't know how to deal with heartbreak.
哦, 那你的处方是什么, Estrogen医生
Oh,and what's your prescription,dr.Estrogen?
享受哈根达斯, 看爱情片 直到和你的周期同步?
Eat haagen-dazs and watch love actually,till your periods sync uP.
对了, 就是这样
yeah,that's the stuff.
哦上帝啊
Oh,my god.
你玩这个多长时间了?
How long have you been doing this?
当我还是孩子的时候我父亲就教我射击
Well,my dad taught me to me shoot when I was a kid.
当我孤单或者压抑的时候 我都到这里来, 提醒我自己...
Whenever I'm feeling lonely or depressed,I come here,and it reminds me that...
枪是很好玩的
guns are fun.
你知道, Ted一直对枪很反感
um,you know,ted is kind of against guns.
所以Ted永远也不能知道我在玩这个
And that's why ted's never going to find out about this.
哇哦, 我拿枪是不是有点威胁你的意思?
Whoa,that sounded kind of scary with me holding a gun,didn't it?
不, 我是说, 别把这事告诉Ted
No,I-I just mean,please don't tell ted.
你想试试看吗?
You want to try?
当然
Only hell yeah.
哦是的, 这就是我想要的
Oh,yeah,yeah,this is what I needed.
一直来我都感觉很无力 但是这个...
I felt so powerless this whole time,but this...
太有力了
this is power.
这真是...
This is...
我应该提醒你有很大的后座力
I should of mentioned the recoil.
我得告诉你, 我回家的时候 他居然在笑, 你是不是和他上床了?
I got to hand it to you,when he got home,marshall was smiling-- did you sleep with him?
因为我好像已经有3天没有提出这个要求了
'Cause I was actually,like,three days away from suggesting that.
有时候, 你们需要做的就是接触他阴柔的一面
Sometimes,all you need is to get in touch with your feminine side.
太好了!
yeah,yeah!
好吧, 恭喜你
Well,congratulations.
你是这整个夏天里唯一能让他开心的人
You're the first person to cheer him up all summer.
- 你赢了 - 哦, 那我能得到什么?
You win. Oh,what do I win?
让我告诉你会赢得什么: 这个周末我会带你出去
I'll tell you what you win: I'm taking you away this weekend.
真的吗?
You are?
这真是太棒了
That's so nice.
是的, 我叔叔和阿姨在Montauk有一幢海滩别墅 那里真是太浪漫了
Yeah,my aunt and uncle have a beach house out in montauk,oh,it's really romantic.
我叔叔在那里好像有过3次浪漫史
My uncle's had like three affairs there.
哇哦, 肯定是幢不错的房子 我见过你叔叔的照片
Wow,must be a nice house,I've seen pictures of your uncle.
一切都会很完美的
This is going to be so great.
我们终于有时间可以独处一下了
We'll finally get some time alone.
不过你觉得Marshall会同意吗?
Are you sure marshall's going to be okay with this?
是的, 当然
Yeah,absolutely.
伙计, 我已经好多了
Dude,I'm doing much better.
事实上, 你可以开我的车去
In fact,take my car.
- 真的吗? - 是的
Really? Yeah.
嘿, 谢谢了...
Hey,thanks...
不管白天还是晚上, 如果需要什么就打电话过来 不过你知道吗, 请一定别打过来
and,hey,if you need anything day or night,just call me-- you know what,please don't call me.
什么? 怎么了?
What?What's wrong?
这是, 嗯, Lily的信用卡帐单
It's,uh,lily's credit card bill.
她肯定是忘记更换她的地址了
She must have forgotten to switch her address.
然后呢?
So?
然后我想知道她在旧金山都花了些什么钱
So,I wonder what kind of charges she's making out there in san francisco.
不不, 看这个一点好处都没有
No.No,no good can come from looking at this.
你好不容易才有这么点好转
You've made too much progress already.
- 我知道, 但是我只是想, 也许... - 绝不!
I know but I just,maybe the-- no!
你会因此感激我的
You're going to thank me for this.
你是一个很好的朋友, Ted
You're a good friend,ted.
8月5日, 一项支出--球票
August 5th,one charge-- tickets.
去哪里呢?
To what?
去看George Clinton & The P-funk全明星秀
George clinton and the p-funk all-stars.
8月10日, 一项支出: 网球场
August 10th,one charge: Tennis emporium.
8月18日, 两项支出: Mario的小餐馆和宠物商店
August 18th,two charges: Mario's bistro and,get this,pet palace.
你们都看到这代表什么了, 对吗?
You guys see what this means,right?
哇哦, Mario的小酒馆
Wow,mario's bistro.
多好的卖弄风骚的地方
What a perfect place to whore around.
对于我最爱的小Lily是的
Only the best for my little lily pad.
哦, Funk的传说任务George Clinton
Oh,funk legend george clinton,
我真高兴你在演唱会上点了我的名字 并且邀请我上台和你共舞
I am so glad you spotted me at your concert and dragged me onstage to dance with you courtney cox-style.
Courtney Cox是老友记中Monica的扮演者
哦, 我也很高兴你同意和我一起打网球
And I'm so glad you agreed to play tennis with me.
你知道吗, Marshall试图 让我和他一起打网球有9年了
You know,marshall tried to get me to play tennis for nine years,
但是我从来没有做过 因为我从来没有真正爱过他
but I didn't do it,because I never truly loved him.
我给你带了一个礼物
I got you a gift.
一个白鼬
A ferret.
哦, 我得去隔壁的宠物商店给他买点吃的
Oh,I'll buy it some food next door at the pet palace.
哦, 我一直很想要一只 但是Marshell一直有什么白鼬恐惧症
Oh,I've always wanted one,but marshall had this secret phobia of ferrets.
我打赌他肯定让你发誓别告诉任何人
I bet that's something he made you promise not to tell nobody.
的确是这样的
It was.
我爱你, Funk的传奇George Clinton
I love you,funk legend george clinton.
我也爱你, Lily
I love you,too,lily.
没错, Marshell 她现在完全属于我了
That's right,marshall,she's all mine.
现在我打算让她玩玩我的头发
Now I'm gonna let her play with my hair.
这是我见过的最疯狂的事情
that's the craziest thing I've ever heard.
是的, 你为什么害怕白鼬?
Yeah,why are you afraid of ferrets?
他们很可爱啊
They're adorable.
Robin, 因为他们就像毛茸茸的 和管子似的老鼠
Because,robin,they're like fuzzy,tube-shaped rats.
还有, 这些消费似乎是一个月之前的
Plus,those charges are from,like,a month ago.
的确
Exactly.
要看新的记录 你必须去网上查看她的账户
For new charges,you have to go to her online account.
也许你们能看到2个小时前的信用卡使用记录
You can see credit card activity from,like,two hours ago.
但是, 你们知道, 还是别这么干
But,you know,don'T.
你干什么要说话?
Why do you talk?
你为什么要开口说话?!
Why do you talk?!
他需要输入她的密码 他应该不会有密码的吧
He needs her password.It's not like he has her password.
哦, 好吧, 他有她的密码
Ooh,this is good,he has her password.
这是今天早些时候的记录: 5日在kellett宾馆
There's a charge from earlier today: The kellett hotel on 5th.
我无法相信这个
I don't believe this.
Lily回到纽约了
Lily's back in new york.
我无法接受这个
I can't believe this.
Lily已经在纽约了?
Lily's in new york?
我以为她一回来就会打电话给我的
I-I guess I've been thinking when she got back,she'd call me.
这是我这整个夏天都能这么坚强的唯一原因
That's really the only reason I've been able to hold it together so far this summer.
他整个夏天都很坚强?
This has been "holding it together"?
好吧, 我打电话给她
Okay,you know what?I'm calling her.
- 不行 - Ted, 把电话给我
No. Ted,give me the phone.
你不能打电话给她 这毫无用处
You're not calling her,this changes nothing.
你们, 给我过来
You,come here.
听着, 这个周末我们不在的时候 你要看好他, 保证他不给那个宾馆打电话
Look,while we're away this weekend,can you keep an eye on him,make sure he doesn't call that hotel?
你想让我当保姆?
You want me to babysit him?
20美元
20 bucks.
一个小时
An hour.
还有买匹萨的钱
And money for pizza.
哦好吧, 如果这次不免费 以后每次出去你就会看到
Uh,yeah,how about you do it for free or every time we hang out,you have to watch this?
过来
Come here.
我亲爱的蓝眼睛宝贝, 美丽的双唇 哦, 甜蜜啊....
My little blue-eyed baby,baby lips. Ooh,ooh,sugar,sugar...
好吧, 我不要钱了! 别再这么恶心了
okay,I'll do it!Stop being a couple.
Marshall.
Marshall, marshall! Marshall,marshall!
Ted, 我知道我不该这么做 但是我必须这样!
Ted,I know I shouldn't do this,but I have to!
- 你打电话给她... - 我们在一起已经9年了!
You call her we were together for nine years!
- 我们在一起经历了这么多事情... - 只会让事情更加...
And everything we've been working so hard for is completely flushed down the toi...
你好, 请接Lily Aldrin的房间
hello,lily aldrin's room,please.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 现在就挂机 - Ted, 我现在不能挂
Hang up now. Ted,I can't hang up now.
离弦之箭, 我知道你不同意这样做
The missiles are in the air,and I know that you don't approve.
你好
Hello.
呃, 是一个男人接的电话
Uh,a guy answered.
有一个男人在她房间里面
There's-there's a guy in her room.
我亲自过去
I'm going down there.
伙计, 你不能这么做
Barney: Dude,you can't do that.
我必须过去, 我必须告诉她我爱她
Have to go down there,and I have to tell her I love her;
我会求她回心转意 如果需要的话我甚至可以下跪
I have to beg her to take me back,even if I have to get down on my knees.
Marshall, 你不能这么做
Marshall,you can't do that.
哦, 是吗? 为什么不能?
Oh,really,why not?
Ted: 第56天
Ted: 56 days.
我们花了这么长时间才有这点成果
That's how long it took me to get right about here.
因为你是个可怜虫
Because you're pathetic!
抱歉, 但是现在, 你不是真正的Marshell
I'm sorry,but right now,you are not marshall.
你是一个可悲的, 抱怨连天，喜欢闻洗发水 的Marshall的灵魂
You are the miserable,whining,shampoo-sniffing ghost of marshall,
老实说，Lily是不会给像你这样的男人 机会的
and frankly,a guy like you doesn't have a shot in hell with a girl like lily.
你知道谁有机会吗?
You know who might have a shot somewhere down the line?
Marshall.
那个真正的Marshall
The real marshall.
但是如果你现在就过去，你就会坏了真正 的Marshall的事, 他永远都不会原谅你的
But if you go down there right now like this,you're going to blow it for him,and he's never going to forgive you.
当然, 不管我说什么, 你都选择背道而驰 好吧, 那就祝你有一个开心的周末
Of course,whatever I say,you're just going to do the opposite,so have a great weekend.
尽情糟蹋你自己的生活吧
Good luck screwing up your life.
快点, Robin
Come on,robin.
我们是不是还能借你的车用一下?
is it still okay if we borrow the car?
勇敢
Bold.
勇敢的用车吧
Bold to go for the car.
什么?
What?
我什么都没说
I didn't say a thing.
你觉得我刚才太过分了
You think I was too hard on him.
我可什么都没说
I didn't say a thing.
我不能相信你居然指责我对他太过分了
I can't believe you're accusing me of being too hard on him.
是你说的"严厉的爱"
You're the one who said "tough love.
是的, "严厉的爱", 但是并不代表要给他讨绞索
" Yeah,tough love,not "hand the guy a noose.
哦, 给他把七毫米的枪就可以
" Oh,but it's okay to hand him a nine millimeter?
是的, 他告诉我的
Yeah,he told me.
那么你是一个枪痴吗?
So you're a gun nut?
不, 我是一个火枪爱好者
No,I'm a gun enthusiast.
- 你知道每年多少人被杀吗? - 至少保护我免收....
Do you know how many people are killed each year the second amendment protects my right to bear arms...
好吧好吧
all right,all right,all right.
我刚才是有点太过分了
I was too hard on him.
有那么一点
A little.
我打电话给Barney, 看看事态怎么样了
I'm going to call barney,see how they're doing.
我是Barney
go for barney.
哦嘿, 你们都在哪里呢?
Oh,hey,where are you guys?
我们在一个募捐会上 帮助一群年轻女性为大学社团筹钱
We're at a fundraiser,helping young women raise money for community college.
脱衣舞馆, 很好
Strip club,nice.
Marshall怎么样了?
Is marshall okay?
他在这里, 他现在很好, 等等别挂
yeah,he's here and he's great.Uh,hang on.
Marshall?
告诉Ted...
Tell ted that--
已经完了?
Already?
什么? 什么啊哦?
What?What uh-oh?
他不见了
He's gone.
你把他弄丢了?
You lost him?
真不敢相信 他会直接去宾馆找她的
I can't believe this.He's going to go down to that hotel.
伙计, 你说的没错
Crap,you're right.
好吧, 我这里有个计划
Okay,okay,here's the plan,here's the plan.
你直接去宾馆拦住他
You go down to the hotel and find him.
我呆在这里跳舞
I'll stay here and get a lap dance.
- 数三下, 1, 2...
- Barney! On three.One,two... barney!
你叔叔的家里有没有热水浴缸
Was there a hot tub at your uncle's place?
有一个很不错的
A really nice one.
嗨, 你能告诉我Lily Aldrin住在哪个房间吗?
Hi,uh,could you tell me what room lily aldrin's in?
Marshall.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我上去找了Lily 准备好了说词
Well,I went up to lily's floor,and I had this little speech in my head--
就是那些我这个夏天以来一直想告诉她的话 爱情, 忠诚, 信任
everything I've been wanting to say to her all summer about love,loyalty,respect.
我敲了门
I knocked on the door.
那么你打了Lily的新男朋友?
So you knocked out lily's new boyfriend?
是的
Yeah.
不过不是Lily的男朋友
It wasn't lily's boyfriend.
什么? 那是谁?
What? Who-- who was it?
他叫Joey Adalian 虽然他作为惯偷一年里面换了无数个名字
Ted: His name was joey adalian,although he went by a number of aliases in his years as an identity thief.
很明显, 早些时候...
Apparently,earlier in the summer...
哦, 真是尴尬
lily: Oh,this is so embarrassing.
我发誓我有零钱的
I-I could have sworn I had some change.
我知道的, 抱歉
I know,I know.I'm sorry.
哦, 有了
Oh,here we go.
不对, 这是一个钮扣
No,that's-that's a button.
这只是一个钮扣
It was a button.
你们这里接受信用卡支付吗?
Do you,uh,take credit cards?
哦是的
Yes,I do.
那么说她没有回来 她也没有新的男朋友?
So lily's not back in town,and she doesn't have a boyfriend?
是个好消息, 不是吗?
Th-that's good news,right?
是的
Yeah.
我也不知道
I don't know.
那些帐单是我和她保持联系的唯一的方法
Those credit card charges were the only remaining connection I had to her.
我不知道她现在在哪里 也不知道她在做什么
I don't know where she is or what she's doing.
她是我的全部, 但是现在, 她不见了
She was my whole life,man,and now she's-she's gone.
你知道, 大学的第一天, 我很害怕
You know,first day of college,I showed up,I was so freaked out,and-
我去了我的寝室, 看到了我的室友 他躺在床上, 脚架在墙上
and I got up to my room,and there was my roommate,lying on the bed with his feet up on the wall.
带着耳机, 脸上带着微笑 一副不屑一顾的样子
Had headphones on,big smile on his face like he just didn't give a crap.
开心
Happy.
自信
Confident.
不担心任何事情
Not afraid of anything.
那个人就是你
That guy was you.
在认识Lily之前的你
You before you met lily.
Ted?
啊?
Yeah?
那天我磕药了
I was high that day.
对
I was.
我太兴奋了, 觉得你是院长
I was so high,I thought you were the dean.
我想说的是, 有一个另外的你 没有Lily的你, 而不是现在的你
Wh-what I'm saying is there's a version of you without lily,and it's not this.
你不能让Lily偷走你的人 就像那个男人偷走了她一样
You can't let lily steal your identity the wathat guy stole hers.
明白
Okay.
好的, 决定了
Okay,resolved.
从明天开始, 我就没事了
Starting tomorrow,I'm going to start being okay.
干杯
Cheers.
但是他并没有做到 也许这就是生活
But he wasn't,'cause that's not how life works.
第二天, 他找到了她的一个袜子还是什么的 于是我们又重新回到了起点
The next day,he found one of her socks or something,and we were back to square one.
然后有一天上午...
And then,one morning...
Ted, 我想你应该过来看看
ted,I think you should see this.
哦不, 又怎么了?
Oh,no,what now?
Marshall, 你在干什么?
Marshall,what are you doing?
今天是周日
It's sunday.
该吃点煎饼了
It's pancakes day.
他花了整整67天才终于作出这个恶心的煎饼
It took him 67 days and one really disgusting batch of pancakes...
真不错
so good.
的确不错
So good.
但是至少, Marshall又起死回生了
But marshall had come back from the dead.
因为棒球, 脱衣舞女, 还有枪都不能解决问题
Because while baseball,strippers,and guns can help,
能够治疗一个破碎的心的东西 只有时间
the only thing that can really heal a broken heart is time.
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
sync:fisherchen www.YDY.com
www.YDY.com Proudly Presents